I said take off your clothes.
Now.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[STUTTERING] Ah!
Don't come near me! I'm telling
you, stay away from me!
No! No taking off
of the clothes!
I'm not that kind of girl!
What are you talking about?
I didn't say all your clothes.
Just your sweater.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Huh?
- [DOOR CLOSES]
(In Korean) Hello, Mr. Jeon!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
(In Korean) Hello.
(In Korean) Shall we begin?
(In Korean) Yes.
[IN UNISON] Fighting!
Miss Ria. She's our stylist.
She will get your measurements.
Get yourself some clothes.
Wait a sec. What's wrong
with my clothes?
You have to look presentable.
Hey now, Kpaps.
For your information,
I am 10% talent
and 90% confidence.
No OOTD required, alright?
Miss Ria.
Yes, sir?
Jacket.
Jacket... jacket.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh...
(In Korean) This one?
(In Korean) Yes.
You can set up in the room.
Okay, sir.
(In Korean) Thank you.
- Let's go, girls.
- (In Korean) Thank you.
Hannah, fighting!
Take off your sweater now.
Please.
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
You can't look out of place
beside me.
This guy is so full of himself.
(In Korean) Stupid.
Hey, you!
Stop calling me stupid.
Stop acting like one.
Hmph!
Come.
[HANNAH] Come, come!
Here.
[HANNAH] Okay. Smile!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DANIEL] What are you doing?
I'm just checking
if it suits me.
See? It's not out of place.
No, no, no.